<!--
  Copyright 2012 The Android Open Source Project

  Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  You may obtain a copy of the License at

      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  limitations under the License.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Sangria Doctrine</string>

    <string name="dummy_section_text">Section %1d is just a dummy section.</string>

    
    <string name="home_title">The Sangria Doctrine</string>
    <string name="home_main_text">\"The Home Of The World-Finalist Self-Health Lecture Series\"</string>
    <string name="main_image_text">Sangria</string>
    
     <string name="doctrine_title">The Doctrine</string>
    <string name="doctrine_main_text">\"Let me tell you a story\"\n\n
        Falijah Hume leans back in his tweed armchair.\n\n
        \"It was the early aughts and Black Box Wines was sweeping the nation.  
        Never before had there been a mass market premium box wine.  My wife 
        and I had just returned from a seven month sabbatical in Berlin.  
        The private elevator to our condo was broken so we had to walk down the 
        hall for the first month back in the states.  Box wine was simply convenient 
        to carry!\"\n\n
        Sniffles purrs while sitting in the sun atop a wild stack of books.  Sniffles 
        has grey fur that appears to be golden in the evening sun.  Sniffles is Dr. 
        Hume’s cat, or as he calls her with a chuckle, \“my administrative assistant\”.\n\n
        \"The box wine was actively damaging our sensitive palettes.  I don’t know, it was 
        like we could taste the plastic.  We hadn’t yet been to the grocery store so we had 
        no fresh fruit.  I turned to my wife and I said ‘Look around us.  I bet we could find 
        some way to turn what we have into Sangria’.  So that’s what we did.  We looked around 
        the apartment in search of ingredients for Sangria.\"\n\n
        \"You have to keep an open mind when trying to make Sangria.  Ask yourself about every 
        item you grab: ‘Could this be Sangria?’\”\n\n
		Sniffles jumps down onto Dr. Hume’s lap.\n\n
		\"The answers may surprise you.\'\"\n\n

        </string>
        
    <string name="hume_title">Dr. Falijah Hume MeHD</string>
    <string name="hume_first_text">Dr. Hume emigrated from Texas in the early 90s and made the 
        eastern United States his home.  Assimilation into American culture was hard for him and 
        made worse by his Anosmia, a rare disorder resulting in the inability to smell.</string>
    <string name="hume_second_text">\"People always tell me that when you lose a sense, another 
        becomes heightened. That must be why I have such a keen sense of wonder.\"</string>
    <string name="hume_third_text">Following his patriation to the United States, Dr. Hume developed 
        The Sangria Doctrine.</string>
        
    <string name="samberg_title">Father Max Samberg</string>
    <string name="samberg_first_text">Author of Hummus for the Homeless, Father Samberg has traveled 
        the world sharing his insight.</string>
    <string name="samberg_second_text">\"The convective currents in steeping tea are life energy.  
        You need to absorb that energy into your life.  You need to drink it in by surrounding yourself 
        with mugs of steeping tea.\"</string>
    <string name="samberg_third_text">Father Samberg infuses his teachings with a unique blend of god-proven 
        perspectives.</string>
        
    <string name="bergston_title">Don Bergston, Certified Artisan</string>
    <string name="bergston_first_text">Four-time American artist, Don Bergston has crafted his techniques with
        a rigor undue for most artforms</string>
    <string name="bergston_second_text">\"If you never try, you can never fail. If you give up, you can never 
        achieve your goals. So I say, \'Don\'t try or give up. Succeeding the first time never fails.\'\"</string>
    <string name="bergston_third_text">Don Bergston was the first in a series of Certified Artisans to endorse
        The Sangria Doctrine</string>
        
    <string name="bio_title">Impressive Title</string>
    <string name="bio_first_text">Impressive Feat</string>
    <string name="bio_second_text">Impressive Quote</string>
    <string name="bio_third_text">Impressive Fact</string>
    
        
    <string name="upcoming_title">Upcoming Lectures</string>
    
    <string name="ask_title">Your Friends Of The Sangria Doctrine Are Delighted To Answer Your Questions</string>
    
    <string name="ask_button_text">Send us an email!</string>
    
    
    
</resources>
